Tianting.
It's so late.
What are you doing?
Auntie.
Come with me.
Why are you in my room?
Didn't you just ask me to help you...
It's nothing.
If it's nothing, I'll be going then.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Auntie, you're usually quite busy.
Since you're finally here,
let me offer you a cup of ginseng tea
to ease your fatigue.
Fatigue?
I am feeling tired.
Tianting, why don't you rest first?
I'm heading back to sleep.
Auntie!
Drink it.
Then you can see the one you wish to see.
Come on.
No!
Drink it.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Stay back!
Brother.
It's me.
Tiankun.
Tiankun!
Tiankun, why are you here?
Tiankun.
Tiankun!
Tiankun, are you okay?
Tiankun, what's wrong?
What a coincidence.
You're all here.
You've worked hard too, Brother.
Drink this.
I-I can't drink this.
Wait!
Tiankun!
Stay back!
Father!
Something's wrong with Tiankun, Father!
Open the door!
Father, Tiankun is trying to kill me!
Open the door, Father!
Something's wrong with him!
Father, save me!
Tiankun... something's wrong with him!
Something's wrong with him!
Father! Father, come quickly!
Have you noticed something off
about those two Qi Family brothers?
Those two brothers
are scheming to lead the Qi Family.
As for that old fox, Qi Lianhai...
As long as I can get what I want,
I couldn't care less about the rest.
But now it seems,
that old fox Qi Lianhai
just wants me dead.
He refuses to join the other three's plan.
What a shortsighted family.
Right now, the Qi Family's
original talisman book is still missing.
And the Wan Family still hasn't shown up.
The deadline for that thing's Reckoning
on The Four Families is eight days away.
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
Eldest daughter of the Sheng Family, yes?
Heard your live-in son-in-law was stolen.
Isn't that a coincidence?
My fiancée was stolen, too.
Who exactly are you?
We both want to take back what's ours.
Why don't we sit down for a drink?
Let's have a proper chat.
The Sheng Family's proud eldest daughter
was dumped by a mere live-in son-in-law.
That brat is absolutely despicable.
Despicable. Utterly despicable.
An arrogant brat like you
daring to fight me for Mei Jiushuang?
It's completely laughable.
Li Xiao.
What did you give me to drink?
I'm dizzy.
I found aphrodisiac powder in your room.
Sheng Lingyu.
You went all out for that piece of trash.
Too bad he didn't take the bait.
What on earth...
what are you trying to do?
Since he has no feelings for you,
why be hung up on one person?
There are plenty of men in this world.
Perhaps one is right in front of you.
Let me run the Sheng Family for you,
and get revenge on that bastard.
Let go! Let go of me!
Let me go!
Let go!
Li Xiao!
Li Xiao, what are you doing?
Let me go!
Get away! Li Xiao!
Disgusting!
Bastard!
I'll make you pay!
You... don't you try anything!
What do you mean "try anything"?
You're the one I married.
I can do
whatever I want.